Rajeev, I should.
Hey, hi, Pramod. Hi, Shubhankar.
Hey, hi Matt.
Hi, Matt. Good morning.
Hey guys, good afternoon. Good evening. How is everybody?
Rob.
Good morning.
Huh.
I know Erik should be jumping on here shortly.
Okay, no worries.
Everyone, good morning.
Oh good, and this is recording. I forgot to record yesterday's session, so I figured out how to set recordings automatically when the meeting starts. So all these should be recorded automatically now.
Awesome, yeah, and if you're missing any, I can, I can, I think I've been recording more, so I can just share a quick.
Yeah.
Quick synopsis if you need it.
Yeah, if you wouldn't mind sharing for yesterday, that would be great, because then I'm just throwing all these in our meta wiki so we have a page for them. So we basically have every stand up then. Perfect.
All right, good morning all. So we have one new individual, Rajeev. I'll go ahead and let you say hi to the team.
Hey, hi everyone. So I have joined this project from today onwards, Matt, and I will be mainly taking care of the project management responsibilities from Bounteous side. I might not be involved in any hands on work, but I will try as much as possible to coordinate everything.
From other.
Right, so mainly with just the US, India, it's just, it's hard for me to do the backlog by myself, especially with the team going 100 miles an hour over there. And so, you know, we just thought we'd spin up project management, so then it kind of helps, and then he's on their side, and then he can kind of help make sure that, you know, they're keeping busy, keeping the board up to date. Yeah, and so I'll be working a lot with him to get the
The boys going.
Great, pleasure to meet you, Rajeev.
Thank you, thank you, man.
Perfect. So yeah, so I'll go ahead and kick us off today. So yeah, so as I mentioned yesterday, I'm starting to get the backlog going, but I had some prerequisites I needed to *** **** out. I was working on the flows yesterday and just making sure I could get the screenshots all generated. I made some tweaks so that I can actually export these to our Lucid board just so that then we can kind of have them up there and just makes it a little bit easier.
So I got those updated and on the Lucid board right now. And so now we actually have, and I shared all these with the team yesterday, which also I updated the script yesterday. Also, since we are targeting iOS, I had it use my iOS emulator locally for the prototype, so that this way then we can start to see the screens.
with which how they would show up on an actual iPhone. So these were all re-rendered, as I said, using the iOS emulator. And then the screenshots were taken. So Erik, Matt, let me know if you guys need me to send over the latest sets. I feel like Christine should be good, but just let me know. I can always shoot these over. I didn't change any of the layouts or add any new screens. Literally just rendered in this iOS and then just try to make sure that I have a flow up here for everything.
as well. And then additionally, when we were doing some digging, it also made this nice little mermaid diagram of just like the flow of the actual calls that it makes to like the backend. And so today I'm going to try and put together all the screens, all the features and functionality of each screen. And then in the meta repo, I'm going to go create a whole side section where then I basically like
talk about the prototype, show every screen, what feature, backend, and then I'll use all of that data once I have it and then generate a backlog because then by that time I have everything that I need for the backlog. And so that's my basically today and tomorrow update, even though I will be here tomorrow. With that, I'll go ahead and pass it off to the team.
Pramod, if you want to go next.
I do know the team does have some questions today because they were asking a whole bunch of questions. Some of them I knew the answers to and the rest of them just like, let's just ask the scribble team and use our, you know, now we actually have questions for our stand up. So, or they'll send them to you in an e-mail. Sorry, go ahead, come on.
Yeah, Shah.
Yeah, I think short one from my side. I think just following up on the access request. So Erik, we got the GitHub one. I did respond with a couple of things. I think you already made us maintainer now. And just before the call, I was checking, I was able to see the ad member.
So I think we are good on the GitHub side. You had the question about the iOS one. There again, I think there's no separate prerequisite, but it just, once we start having iOS builds, it starts eating up the build minutes, free build minutes, and so you'll probably want to put a...
Payment plan there.
All right, I can do that.
Yeah, and I think the AWS one, I guess you're working through it, so we'll probably look for updates on that one from you.
That's it for me, Pankaj. You wanna go next?
OK.
Yeah, Pramod, I think you covered most of the things, so should we start asking the questions that we have yesterday?
I think that.
Do we want to run through the team first? Run through the team, give everybody, give their updates, and then we'll do that as an after-party item.
Yap.
So then everybody can just put all their questions together and we can just run through all the questions at the end. So just give any updates now and we'll run through the team and then we'll do that in an after party.
Yeah, I got it. Sure. So I mostly, I was going through all the documentations, the screen walkups that you shared yesterday and accordingly. So what I'm doing is I'm actually validating some of the architectural decisions that we are going to make specifically on back and front end both sides. And along with that, I'm.
trying to set up a scaffolding application, at least on the IS side, which will let us validate all the build part and you know, how do we publish and distribute the application using test flight and all, all that setting I'm doing on my local machine. So that's where I am. We have kind of.
set up some part of, you know, the IS, how the application will structure. Only the structure, not exactly the real screens and all, but the overall architecture of the application, how authentication and everything will be managed and then. Along with that, I'm trying to validate other technical decision items that we have.
So like me, you had a PR on our temporary Bitbucker repo for where, you know, the scribble, the scribble mobile, it was what it was called, you had created an initial PR in there. So just remember to move that over to the GitHub now that we have it. I moved my PR over there yesterday as well. So just reminding you, move your prompts PR over.
Hello.
I will, the only reason I have not done that is I'm still planning on the back end side. Once we have, because we'll have to create the repo and start moving. I don't want to keep another POC there, so we are doing some validations and all. Eventually I'll move everything together.
So we are planning data action, everything we are planning, keeping data as the source of truth. So nothing specific but bucket and all. That's why on a couple of items we are still holding up and all, but eventually we are planning everything based on GitHub only.
Okay, I can go next. Okay, so yesterday after our discussion, Rob, I did compare my schema draft that I created with the POC schema and that eventually bring up some certain questions that we are going to ask after I even go through.
through the updates. I can even post them in the chat right now so that everyone can start, can have a look over the questions. And today, me and Pankaj also connected related to some of the points that we are going to discuss. And also, I will be targeting to.
put certain tickets assigned to myself tomorrow and try to close them as some of the decision. Pankaj have already provided the documentation in the handbook that we have. So yeah, that's all.
what I have done today.
Okay, I can go next. Okay, please go ahead.
Okay, I go.
Thanks, Shubhankar. So I was working on the test management tool. I'm trying to set it up on my local. So I was successfully able to do this QV tool. Like I did some exploration today on that. Like I'm able to create test plan, test cases, and then we should be able to import the test case as well after we generate through Claude. So all that exercise I have done today.
So I'm just waiting for a go ahead to set this up on one of the VMs and then start using from there.
Also, I have also doing the analysis on the latest screens that shared by Rob, so I will be continue working on that.
Yeah, that's all that might say. Thank you.
Hi everyone. Yesterday and today as well, I am basically going through the code which Pankaj has pushed on the bit bucket. So I have also checked the MD files like the project MD files, the meta base. I also connected with Pankaj regarding how he has.
updated the flow and introduced this mock screens. So right now I'm in that process of reviewing the code as of now. Second, I am also looking in for the various access requests. Today I got cloud access.
But I'm still waiting for machine level access to set up code and dev tools, like installing dependencies in terminal and all. So I'm still not being able to do that. Once those things are done, I will be able to run code and have more detailed analysis on that.
For now, I'm also be needing GitHub request, like GitHub approval for me so that I can, once we start coding and development, we can, I can push the code to GitHub. So that is all from my side.
Yeah, so all everyone should be getting the GitHub once today, because we are now maintainers on the GitHub report, so we'll be adding all of the team members, so you can look for that notification.
Thank you, Pramod.
Okay, I guess then we can go forward with the questions.
Alright, who wants to start?
Just real quick, Rajeev, Rob, the machine level access that Shubhankar just referenced, is that on our end? Is that something that, okay, gotcha.
That's on our end, that's on our end, that's RIT.
Okay, over to you, Pankaj.
Because many of the engineers are on, sorry, many of the engineers were on Windows, and so we had to get them on Macs, especially because of the iOS side of this.
Gotcha. Makes sense. Thank you.
I think we can, I can start with the questions.
So one of the question I had in mind is because I was going through the overall flu as well as for the App Store or Google Play Store, maybe in future requirements and all, we'll be needing some hosted pages, specifically like for invitation, you know, when somebody wants to join and also are we.
Even even if we like leave out invitation and all, we will have to provide the privacy policy and couple of other links as part of the overall documentation when we try to deploy the application on either Play Store or Apple Store and all. So are we are we looking for?
like a separate hosting for all this or is it like in the existing scribble site or somewhere we'll be hosting all those pages.
We could certainly host them on our site. That's what we do currently for the B2B version of the game. Privacy policy, all that's on scribble.co. Rob, what is best practice for something like this?
So do, I mean, we can ask the team, do you guys want to spin up a separate repo where we do this? Is this something where we can share the B2B side or do we want this to be completely separate? I feel like we want this to be separate products, so these would be our own separate pages. So I think more than likely what he's stating is we'll need to create a separate repository for that.
where then we can create the hosting for it and probably its own AWS to stand it all up and everything like that. Is that what you're talking about?
Yes, I'm certainly in favor of setting up something separate because we'll be, we probably might be needing some couple of pages, as I said, for invitation, maybe for sharing or some other things as well. So it's better we set up a separate repository, privacy policy, or, you know, those kind of, those are like global documents.
I don't know, like we can decide either we keep it on, you know, whatever we will develop or maybe on the main scribble.
site or something, but definitely we would need something to host a couple of pages, not very extensive pages, but yeah, to start downloading flow and a couple of other things we might be needing some pages.
So it probably makes more sense to just make another GitHub repo for this.
Yes.
On the scribble side.
We are going with one repo, so we don't need probably a separate repo. We'll be getting some folders for app backend. We can create one more for let's public website or something.
Do you want to do this with a monorepo? I'm asking you, do we prefer a monorepo or do we want to be a separate repo? Because I know that Karuna is going to ask for a separate repo for QA, so we might as well get our repo asks out now.
Yap.
I'll confirm the repo structure tomorrow. I'm still validating a couple of things in terms of deployment and all, but so yeah, based on that, either we'll, if we don't go with mono repo, then yes, we'll create a repo, small repo, else we'll create a folder for that.
Okay, so let's defer that question till tomorrow, and I'll let you answer that yourself with what you would prefer, and then we'll get that created on their side.
That's only about the repo, but yes, we will be needing a kind of a hosted site which will render some of the pages.
Correct.
I think, Nikhil, you had a couple of questions also, right? You want to go ahead with them?
Yeah.
Okay, yeah, I have some questions here. So let's start with the first one. So my first question is related to sign up. Do we actually want to capture the birth date or age verification and consent at the sign up from the day one?
Rob, we had talked about how there's going to be two waves of this, one being the plus 13, one being under 13 for the additional kind of review that we'd have to go through with Apple.
Um...
Would it be wise just to have this in place for both of those?
That's what I'm thinking, Nitish, that we collect it, but we, you know, kind of as Eric saying, like we're going to have later on, we're going to work with Apple so we can do miners and target, you know, the miners. So there's an extra like thing that they've added for that. But right now, we're just trying to do just general. And so that just might be something that we just collect right now just to have.
So do we want to like at least have capturing the birth date from the user while signing up, but no differentiation, no restriction for the current app that we are building for a minor, even if it is a minor or adult, we will not be differentiating them.
By using our app, that's what.
We are thinking right now.
I think that's what we were thinking, because basically at that point, we're still following Apple's guidelines, and then their parent would have to have, you know, set that up on their phone as much as they do.
Okay.
Okay, okay.
Okay, so my next question is related to the submissions. Like if a user creates a submission and he wants to share it across multiple channels. So do we want to share a copy of it to every channel that he shares? Or do we want a...
Similar copy, just one copy with an add table or a common link that we will share that will display a common image to all the channels.
How, how could that?
I think that that might be a technical thing we can.
The site, right?
Yeah, because remember sharing is like putting it on Instagram, you know, copying a link to it, you know, sending it an e-mail, Facebook, you know, all those is what sharing is.
But while posting an image here, do we want to have, how is the current application? Do we share multiple?
Um...
a similar image to multiple channels at the same time and the user can react or make comments in a different at different different channels in a different way and can use that image or add it currently differently on a different channels.
Is there something happening right now?
I don't believe so. I mean, right now in the current app or the current prototype, you can only pick one item to share it. We have the composition one where you can pick multiple image to make a new composite image, but you can still only then go just share that one time. You can't pick multiple things and then share them out. Maybe that's a future.
thing that we add where we like allow the multi-select and then the share button allows you to share from that. But I think right now we're just doing a single photo and a single share out through like the share screen. So like if you use like the prototype, it looked like this, where you like click on it and then you just hit share and then you have the share, share to Instagram.
Actually, what?
Navee.
share to say Facebook.
I think what Nitish is trying to ask is if we share a single image across multiple channels, do we separately want to capture any reaction or something that comes in channel because...
Either we combine everything, you know, on if let's say there is only one copy in memory, and you know, if you receive multiple reactions on multiple different channels, do you want to track them separately or you want to, you know, club everything and say that we receive, let's say, 10 like or something, or is it like we receive 2 likes in this channel, 3 likes in that channel, something like that, because that defines how we store all the meta time.
Everything around the images.
So I think you guys are talking about like the emojis when you click on say like an image because that's like...
We'll start with emoji, but yeah, it could expand to other metadata in future, but yeah.
Right, right, right, yeah. So like if you click on, say, one of these, so you're viewing your families, or you're viewing a wall and you're viewing other submissions. And so I go in here and I click on this and then I heart it, and then Sam comes into Alice's and hearts it as well, then you would see an accumulation of two heart emojis on this single wall.
Yes, and then if the same image also exists in some some other wall and you're getting some, you know, hard emojis or something in there as well.
Well, I don't know that that would, I mean, because then you're, so, you know, this person gave this, this person gave that. Does that then make sense to then have two hearts than if this then somehow ended up in like your personal channel or your personal wall?
Cause.
Okay, so I think now I think maybe, okay, so because there is the option where like you can create a picture and then when you get to selecting a wall, you can actually pick multiple walls to put it on. So like when I get to here, I drew this picture, I can check both personal wall and family wall. Don't focus on sharing, I'm just trying to say just adding a story.
to a wall right here. So when you've picked it, you've already gone through your flow of creating the new story, and then you're about to add it to a wall, you can pick multiple walls, and then it basically that picture goes into each individual wall. So then on your personal wall, you can use it to do whatever, it's a separate copy, and then your family wall, it's a separate copy that then people can add emojis to or do whatever they need to.
Go ahead, Erik.
So if I were to post something to my family and then want to say a friend group, I would not necessarily want my family to maybe see the reactions or the comments back that are eventually coming from that friend group. So keeping them separate will be best. Now a nice to have would be in the
a personal archive, if I when I pulled up an image, it was the cumulative from everything. So I might post this to family, friends, and then maybe like a much larger wall with hundreds of people, like a public wall. If I start getting reactions there in my personal wall, I'd like to see, oh, you know, I posted this that day and I got, you know.
100 reactions here and 10 here and a bunch of comments here, but I don't think that should cross over between the walls. That makes sense.
And by the way, Rob, looking at the last image that you have where you are trying to share, let's say, so is there a possibility of, you know, I may not share the image that I draw on my personal wall and I would just share it in the family wall.
Yeah, you can, right, you can pick and choose, because sometimes you might not want to throw it in your personal wall, it just might be for the family. Plus remember each of these individual like walls, you could have, you know, different prompts in there too, so it might not make sense.
Okay.
Is there anything in the current applications, not, I'm not talking about the prototype, but if the image that is posted over a channel, can that be updated again and again?
Or is it a one-time?
So currently there's no plans to update images once they've been posted.
So the user would need to repost a new one, either delete the previous one.
Well, they just accumulate, we don't delete, yeah, I don't delete any of the pictures right now. They would just go create another picture for like today. Because you can actually have multiple pictures for the same wall for like today. So like right here, how we have like today, if we went and then did pick from a prompt and then drew some manual ones, we would see underneath today a section where it had the prompt for the day.
Rob, is there?
Mmh.
And then whatever we picked from this would then show up as a new set within the photos underneath it for today.
There is a there is an edit icon if you see on this sun that you have drawn. So there is an edit icon probably the question is coming because of that.
Oh, okay. Well, all that allows you to do is click and go into it. And then I think I used to allow you to edit and change your story, and maybe that's why that got left behind. But no, you can't change the pictures after they've drawn. You can make the composite pictures after they've been drawn, but that's about it. So like here where you go when you
hit this button right here on one of your walls that it allows you to pick multiple pictures and then they show up on this page where then you can make a composite picture and then you can save this composite picture. So you can make like a whole bunch of like built up composite pictures over time, but you can't edit them after that. This is like as close to editing as we allow.
Yeah.
And also remember that when we're collecting these, because I made the mistake of this, I was collecting the individual stroke data, because when you're drawing these pictures, we record each stroke. So then you can always hit the back button or hit this undo button and it'll just undo the most recent stroke.
And then obviously delete does the whole wall or the whole screen here. But so we keep all of the individual stroke data so that then when we do these like composite pictures down here, there's no white background because here you can see, because I didn't, I was flattening and adding the background and then saving them as a flat.
picture. And then once Erik told me about this screen that he wanted, I fixed it and started keeping the actual data. So then I could actually do to where these will overlap and it's just the strokes. And so newer ones now, if all these pictures were brand new ones, we would have just the stroke data. And then you wouldn't see the white background that this one is like overlaying over this other one and they all like fit perfectly. So then it's just the stroke.
So just kind of keep that in mind. Because as I said, I accidentally flattened them, which is why I said, here's old data, and that's why this is showing up as old data.
Sorry if I understood correctly, we don't want the background here, right? When you're trying to combine the pictures or what?
Correct, correct. That's where we saved the stroke data. So that's each individual stroke that they did while they were drawing the picture. And that's what I use them when I put these up here is this is all the stroke data. You can actually see it like in the new prototype. We do that.
You.
So, we will keep the true data that that's already there, so...
Okay.
Stop data is fine. I was just trying to understand how do we combine. So you are re-rendering, trying to re-render every feature without a background, right? So that.
Mhm.
Correct, correct. Right, because otherwise, right, because otherwise the background would overlay the other images and yeah, and it's just not as nice as it could be.
Again, correctly.
Plus, also, there's some unique things going forward feature-wise that we can add if we keep that stroke data, which we're not implementing this right now, but, like as an example, when you go to give your story and you record a story verbally, one of the ideas that Erik had was what we could do is...
we could play that story back. So like somebody gets, say, like a GIF where it like plays a story where you hear them saying it or a video. And so you hear the words of them saying it, and then you slowly watch the brush data add up to the full picture at the end. And then we just like, you know, we just cut it a little short before it ends the whole thing. So then you see the full picture. You basically got to like watch the drawing of the picture while listening to the person talk about it.
And that's just some of the cool things later on we could do.
Got it.
Got it, Yap.
Okay.
Okay, so that's clear now. So I have one question. I just want to confirmation relating related to the invites. So do we want a shareable link that would actually be shared?
to the contacts and they will accept it or would it be like certain group that if I have certain contact, I will just add them in my group.
This should probably be a terrible link that can be sent via e-mail or text. The part that gets me is that it expires. We've learned in the past version that when we have invites like what that expire, people don't get to them right away, and then it causes this loop of re-invites and a mess. So I just...
would say anything that's created should not expire.
OK, and the sign-up process still.
We will still continue the same afterwards.
Yeah, so basically you would get the e-mail, which would then take you to the static site that we're going to be putting up. You would then see the logo of like, hey, go install the application. You'd go install the application. You'd then sign in. And at that point, then you should then have like the invite link and all that. And then you start then the invite flow and all that.
Mhm.
Okay, yeah, so I have one last question. It is related to the...
Uhh...
Some of the features we post, do we want certain things like reporting that image or blocking a particular image or moderating that image? Do we have any future plans for these as well?
So we had talked about like having the wall owner be almost like the moderator at the beginning because eventually we do want to add comments to like the responses and so we'll have to have then probably the wall creator be the moderator and maybe eventually AI does some kind of like pre-filtering to help a little bit.
Um...
So having said that, yeah, we're going to probably have the whoever is the wall creator is then kind of like the moderator. I don't.
Yeah, that is getting to the question because people could technically draw anything that they wanted. So do we want the moderator to be like allowed to view the pictures and remove the pictures?
The question would be something like if Rob you added me and I started drawing and submit something, right? Would you first moderate it? You will like some of the places you give like your post would be published in an hour or like an hour so that.
Whoops.
You have that time, right? Some certain features can be posted immediately. Our certain, yeah, it will take some time, but we are reviewing it currently. We will post, it will be live in some moment. Something like this. I just want to understand. Is there something?
I don't think we want that right now, Erik. Keep me honest, because that's something I feel like we would add later if we start to notice that, say, people are drawing bad pictures or things that they shouldn't be drawing in pictures, allowing people to then moderate more. I think right now, let's just start simple. And then if we need to add more moderation, we'll just, we'll know as we get the insights as we develop the app.
Yeah, I agree.
Yeah, we're going to learn a lot, especially on the bigger walls. It might come down to, you know, just crowdsourcing, some sort of moderation, where if you get enough reports or downvotes for say, like you hit a critical mass of those, then we just automatically remove it if enough other users find it offensive. So it's something we still have to work out, but for now it should be as simple as possible.
Okay.
I think I got an answer for most of my questions there. That would really help me to update the schemas that we have.
And get it closer.
Perfect.
Thank you, thank you.
I have two small questions. One is, are we expecting or like are we projecting what kind of load would be? I'm not talking about millions of users and all, but per user basis, like how many images or something we are anticipating because I see we are not.
in our, at least in our screens or something, we are probably just trying to render everything in a wall or something, but at some point, do we expect that there will be like thousands of images within one wall or?
Yes.
So, there, there won't be a limit on how many members can be there in a, in a let's say group or one, let's say, and then...
The the amount of images.
So, we will have to probably adjust the screen design in a way that either we do virtual installing or we.
Add some filtering or something, you know, to restrict images.
Yeah, because one of the thoughts was when we, you know, debut this as AWS, we'll put like a QR code up there and then we'll have, you know, some, the first 500 people come on. And so there could be a single wall with 500 people on it sharing all their photos.
Yeah, but I don't like how interesting they would be to draw the photo, so I'm zooming like...
A user may draw like 5 pictures, something with clicking a picture is something else you can click, click under, you know, find pictures a day if you are attending an event or something, but when it comes to draw, you may probably four or five a day of maximum, right?
Yeah.
But we can, we can, like, that's that's sort of big things is that we need to get them.
I think most use cases, right, somebody would only be drawing a couple pictures A day.
Maybe a couple to their personal, like the prompt of the day, and maybe they started to challenge with one of their kids or family members.
Exactly, and the second one I have is, is, is there any plan that we will take it as a, I don't know, like an enterprise, you know, version of it, or maybe we want to support like, you know, different tenants and all, because that that defines exactly how we want to go with the authentication system, you know.
Cognito or something that do we need multi-tenancy support, SSO support? You know, you want to allow somebody to be able to use their official IDs to log in, or is it is it for public, like use your personal ID and...
I feel like Matt, you shared this in that diagram, the PDF that you shared with me where you were talking about like when companies go to purchase this and use this then and they're using the click enterprise, would they then like just use like their enterprise SSO logins and then we would just support that. I think that's what you're talking about.
That's a good question.
Yeah, there's a bit of a loop with the B2B version and this version eventually. Far out where like if somebody's using the B2B version at work, they also have that same profile as the one that supports this version and they can kind of move back and forth. So I think that probably does need to get built in.
I think that's down the road, not at our first.
Yeah, Greg.
Okay.
Because Rob, then then that's something we need to decide now, because if you go with cognitive for authentication, it's quite good even with millions of users and all, but if you want to control per tenant setting, then it may not be the best choice.
Got you, okay. We'll have to put together some options so we can kind of look at that and then can we put together...
Like using Cognito and then what maybe some alternatives are and then get that right up and then maybe we can have that decide that tomorrow.
Sure, I'll look into that.
Perfect, thank you.
All right, do we have any other questions?
But that's all for myself today.
All right, going once, going twice. Anybody else have any follow-ups? We're a couple of minutes over now at 7 minutes.
I have one small question. I wanted to ask, coming to the field level validations, like if you look at it, the sign up screen, like there is e-mail ID and user can enter a name. So we expected that user always have to enter a valid e-mail. So those validations we expect.
Expected to be there, right?
Yes.
Okay, okay, okay. And I also wanted to ask, like, is like once the user draws a picture, is like, is it mandatory to like write the story or they can skip it?
That's a good question because I was wondering that too, do we want them to skip being able to write a story?
I'd say it's mandatory.
I think we need to train people into sharing the story before they can post it. Erik, would you agree?
I agree. I also see use cases where people might need to skip.
Let's take that internally and decide and report back tomorrow.
Sure, and this.
Because I mean, there could be some basic prompts that they're just like drawing to a basic prompt, and then it's like, do I really want to enter a story for that prompt if the prompt was good enough in the detail? But again, I'll let you guys, I'll let you guys, yep, yep, yep.
Or if you're doing it live.
Yap.
Sorry, go ahead, Dad.
Yeah, yeah, similar question also that, like, once they draw the picture, like, do they have to really post in a wall or they can just keep it?
Their account.
But I think that's what the personal wall is. So at the bare minimum, they can just put it in just their personal for them, just themselves.
Yeah.
Yeah, at least they have to put in personal role. Yeah, understand. Yeah, Yap, got it.
Right, yeah, yeah.
I think that's all for now. Thank you.
As of now, we are not we are not allowing user to.
like work in different session or something. Somebody started drawing a very good face or something, spent half an hour. He has Suresh out maybe for another or or.
You know, he may have to take a break or something, so we we require him to post whatever he has done already, or...
At some point, we'll let him stop in between, maybe continue again.
That's a good question.
That's that's a very valid use case specifically for.
Office going people because you get 10 minute break, you started drawing a face, you draw something, you know, head or eyes or something. You have a meeting, you want to come back and see.
Yeah, Rob, what would be the mechanism if I had to close out? I was halfway through a drawing I had to close out. Is that being, is that state being saved or is the app restarting and I'm losing everything that I did?
We'd lose it. We'd have to basically add a new button, I think, to the canvas. So I think we would have to add sort of like maybe like a save and continue or, you know, some kind of button right here that then would basically like allow you to get out of the rest of this flow. And then it just saves it in like a, you know,
finish later state where then you can click back on it and so it'll just show up on the wall as like maybe unfinished and you click on it and then go back and finish it. Now I didn't bake any of that in, that'd be new stuff we would have to add. Let's just, I don't know what I'm thinking.
It may not be, it may not be a button to say we can auto save, maybe you know every like 3 seconds, 5 seconds or something, but yeah, to to retrieve it back and start working on it, that has to be added somewhere and.
Erik, why don't we, why don't we?
It's more or less using the vector strokes or not.
Erik, why don't we discuss that one as well because
I would advocate that you can't save, you can't come back to it. It's designed to be spontaneous. It's designed to be done in a minute. It's like Wordle, you can't start your Wordle, save it, come back, right? I mean, it's just, it's meant to happen in the... Okay, well, this, I think it's just, we should discuss that. I mean, this is...
You can.
Yeah, we can.
That will.
Yeah, there's some adverse side effects of doing that. Perfection.
You know.
Yep, we'll have an answer tomorrow.
Too much thought.
Okay.
Great questions. Are there any more good questions here?
And Claude can draw. I like some of these little doodles it does.
All right. Well, if there are no more questions, everyone have a wonderful day, and I will see everyone here tomorrow.
Awesome. Thanks, Team. Nice to meet everybody. Take care.
As well.
All right. Thank you, everybody. Thanks, everyone. Bye bye.
Sure. Thank you. Bye-bye.
Thanks, all.
Thanks, thanks everyone.
Thank you.